<resources>
    <!-- App title Details-->
    <string name="app_name">Aberystwyth University Open Day</string>
    <string name="welcomepage">Welcome To Aberystwyth</string>
    <string name="departments">Departments At Aberystwyth</string>
    <string name="academicdepartments">Departments At Aberystwyth</string>
    <string name="disclaimers">Health And Safety</string>


    <!-- Activity main strings mainly image button descriptions -->
    <string name="welcomebutton">Image button to navigate to the welcome page</string>
    <string name="talksbutton">Image button to navigate to the talks and events page</string>
    <string name="refreshementsbutton">Image button to navigate to the page with information about the refreshements at Aberystwyth</string>
    <string name="toursbutton">Image button to navigate to the campus tours page</string>
    <string name="gettingaroundbutton">Image button to navigate to the page about getting around Aberystwyth</string>
    <string name="plannerbutton">Image button to navigate to the personal planner page</string>
    <string name="disclaimersbutton">Image button to navigate to view the disclaimers page</string>


    <!-- Welcome activity string to store the welcome message -->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to our open day and to Aberystwyth University</string>
    <string name="message">It isn’t always easy to decide what you want to study
                            and where to go to university but we hope you will
                            find everything you need during our Open Day, to
                            help you with that choice. If you need any further
                            help please get in touch with a staff member in our
                            Admissions Office or in the relevant department,
                            and they will be glad to assist</string>

    <string name="message2">Aberystwyth is a well-established university with a
                            long tradition of academic excellence, but it is also
                            very forward looking. We’re small enough to be
                            friendly and to allow contact across departments,
                            but big enough to have a wide range of study
                            programmes in the Sciences, the Arts and the Social
                            Sciences, in professional and vocational subjects.</string>

    <string name="message3">Aberystwyth is a vibrant university town in a
                            stunning coastal location, with a dynamic social and
                            cultural life centred around the University. There’s
                            a tremendous range of opportunities for sports,
                            societies, activities and volunteering available to
                            you here.</string>

    <!-- Buton descriptions for department events activity -->
    <string name="academic">Button description for academic departments</string>
    <string name="accomodation">Button description for accomodation office</string>
    <string name="admissions">Button description for admissions office</string>
    <string name="careers">Button description for careers office</string>
    <string name="finance">Button description for finance department</string>
    <string name="support">Button description for student support services</string>
    <string name="studentsunion">Button description for the students union</string>
    <string name="studyabroad">Button description for study abroad office</string>
    <string name="welsh">Button description for studying through the medium of welsh</string>
    <string name="sports">Button description for sports at Aberystwyth</string>


    <!-- Text views for disclaimerspage -->

    <string name="emergencyheading">In The Event Of An Emergency</string>
    <string name="safetyheading">Safety</string>
    <string name="workheading">Building Work</string>

    <string name="emergencymessage">Please contact the nearest member of staff
                                    immediately. Instructions in case of fire are
                                    posted in every building, but if they are not to
                                    hand then please vacate the building by the
                                    nearest exit, do not use the lifts, and remain
                                    outside until informed by a member of University
                                    staff that it is safe to re-enter.</string>

    <string name="safetymessage">In the interests of your own safety, please do
                                not touch any materials or apparatus unless
                                specifically invited to do so by a member of staff.</string>

    <string name="buildingmessage">The University is frequently upgrading
                                    and improving facilities for students and
                                    consequently there is some building work taking
                                    place on the Penglais Campus. We apologise for
                                    any inconvienence. </string>







</resources>
